missguided.co.uk 2019-04-08

# Privacy Policy - Missguided

This policy sets out the basis on which personal information about you may be collected and used when you use (whether to just browse or to make a purchase) the following websites: [ www.missguided.co.uk; ](https://www.missguided.co.uk/) [ www.missguidedus.com ](https://www.missguidedus.com/) [ www.missguidedau.com; ](https://www.missguidedau.com/) [ www.missguided.eu; ](https://www.missguided.eu/) [ www.missguidedfr.fr; ](https://www.missguidedfr.fr/) [ www.missguided.com/pl; ](https://www.missguided.com/pl) [ www.missguided.com/de; ](https://www.missguided.com/de) and [ www.missguided.com/es ](https://www.missguided.com/es) and on our mobile with us on Missguided’s official Facebook, Instagram, Twitter and YouTube accounts (“Social Media”), and purchase Missguided items (“Items”) from the Sites and Missguided branded stores (“Stores”) and our partners’ (“Partners”) stores and websites (“Third Party Platforms”). By using the Sites, registering a Missguided Account, interacting with us on Social Media and purchasing Items from the Stores and Third Party Platforms you are accepting and consenting to the terms of this policy. 

Missguided Limited (company number 03235904) (“ML”) and Missguided USA (Finance) Inc (“MUFI”) are the owners and operators of the Sites and the relevant accounts on the Social Media and Missguided Retail Limited (Company number. 10033268) (“MRL”) is the operator of the Stores. Together ML, MUFI and MRL shall in these terms be referred to as “we”, “us”, “our” and “Missguided”. Our headquarters are at Missguided HQ, 75 Trafford Wharf Road, Manchester, United Kingdom, M17 1ES 

We are committed to maintaining your privacy. We are registered as a data controller with the Information Commissioner’s Office. 

We reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. This Privacy Policy was most recently updated on 21st June 2018. 

Did you know you have rights about the information we collect hold and use about you? The below will help to guide you about the rights that you have but first we thought it might be helpful to explain a little bit about the way the we collect data about you, where you can find specific information about the information we collect about you and why we're collecting it. 

###  HOW, WHY AND WHERE? 

We collect information when you use our sites and at other points in your interactions with us. We collect it in different ways but at each point of collection we will notify you - look out for the pop up boxes and banners on the site - these will give you a quick summary of what we're collecting and why. You will have the option of clicking through to get more detailed information (see section "Information Provision" below to find out what information you'll get but you can always ask any questions by contacting at us using contact details below). 

###  WHAT ARE MY RIGHTS? 

**Information provision**
You have the right to be given the following information each time we collect information from you: (a) our identity and contact details; (b) what we're going to use your information for and the legal basis for processing; (c) whether you are obligated to provide the information and the consequences of failure to provide it; (d) who we will share your information with; (e) whether your information will go outside the European Economic Area and if it does what we're doing to protect it; (f) how long we're keeping your data for; (g) your rights in respect of our use of your data (see below); (h) if we're collecting data with your explicit consent, the fact you have the right to withdraw consent at any time; (i) that you can contact the Information Commissioners Office (www. ico.org.uk) or your local supervisory authority for data protection matters if you have a complaint about our use of your information; and (j) if we make any automated decisions about you, the logic involved and the significance and envisaged consequences for you. 

**Access**

You have the right to ask us the following about our use of your information: (a) the purpose of our use; (b) what type of information is used; © who we share your information with; (d) how long we keep your information; (e) what rights you have in relation the information we hold; (f) whether you have a right to lodge a complaint with the Information Commissioner’s Office or other supervisory authority; (g) if we have collected your information from another person, who that person is; (h) whether we make any decisions about you automatically (g) whether your information goes outside the European Economic Area. You can also ask us for a copy of the data we have. 

**Rectification**

You can ask us to correct any details you think we have which are incorrect 

**Erasure**

You can ask us to delete information about you if any of the following apply: (a) it is no longer required by us for the purpose for which we collected it from you; (b) if we collected it with your explicit consent, when you withdraw that consent; (c) if you have grounds to object to us using it (see below) and we do not have any overriding legitimate grounds for using it; (d) if we have unlawfully used your information; (e) if you need us to delete it so that you can comply with a legal obligation. Please note that we may need to keep certain information to comply with our legal obligation or for claims purposes. 

**Restriction**

You can ask us to stop using your information if any of the following apply, (a) you don't think we have the correct details for you; (b) our use is unlawful and you do not want us to delete your information; © when you object to processing (see below); (d) we no longer require the information for the purpose for which we collected it; (e) where we collected the information with your explicit consent (f) if you object to our use (see below) and we do do not have any overriding legitimate grounds for using it; (g) if you need us to delete it so that you can comply with a legal obligation. Please not when you make a request we can still store your information and use it for claims purposes or if it is necessary to protect another person. 

**Portability**

You have the right to ask us to send your information to you or another person where we originally collected your information with your explicit consent. We must provide this in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format. Please note this does not include information which we have inferred or derived, for example, information we have collected about you to understand your shopping habits with Missguided in order to give you a good customer experience. 

**Objection**

You have the right to ask us to stop using your information where we have told you the legal purpose for which we are processing your information is for "legitimate interests" (see above) and you have grounds relating to your personal situation which requires us to stop using your information or where we have collected your information for direct marketing and you want us to stop using it for direct marketing purposes. 

**Automated Decision Making**

You have the right to object to automated decision-making based on your personal data, and to request human intervention in any such decision. 

###  children 

The Sites are not intended for use by children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If you are under 13 do not use the Sites or provide any information about yourself including without limitation your name, address, email address or any screen name or user name you may use. If we learn that we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe that we may have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at the address below. 

###  social media 

By interacting with us on the Social Media (including without limitation joining our official Missguided group/page or following us on the Social Media, “liking”, “retweeting”, writing a comment in relation to a page on the Social Media) (“Interacting” or “Interaction” (as applicable)) you agree to our interaction with you on the Social Media and the processing of your information accessed on the Social Media in accordance with that Social Media platforms terms of use and privacy policy. The information about you that may be collected when you Interact with us on the Social Media may include without limitation your name, your user profile, your age, your preferences, choices and viewpoints with regards to the topic or subject matter of the relevant Social Media page, your photos and other images and your videos. Your Interaction with us on the Social Media may also involve you submitting a photo or video of you (“Your Image”) to us. We will only use Your Image or other personal information outside of the terms of use or privacy policy of the Social Media platform if you consent to us doing. 

Please let us know if at any time you wish us to stop interacting with you on the Social Media or using any of your information on the Social Media by contacting us at the details set out below. By Interacting with us (whether on the Sites, Social Media or otherwise) you grant to Missguided a perpetual, worldwide, royalty-free license to use Your Image and Contributions for the purposes of promoting, advertising and endorsing Missguided and Missguided’s goods and services, including without limitation for the purposes of your participation in any promotional activity for the same, and in any media including without limitation television, Social Media, on our Sites, in print and outdoor advertising materials. We may want to use Your Image and Contributions for additional purposes which will be detailed when we collect Your Image and/or in any promotional terms and conditions which will be featured on our Promotions Terms page. 

###  how do i exercise these rights? 

If you want to exercise any of these rights please contact our customer care team at informationrights@missguided.com
